export const Quizdata = [
  {
    id: 1,
    quiz: [
      {
        question: "What is Vue?",
        answer: 0,
        options: ["A framework", "A library", "A type of hat"],
        selected: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is Vuex used for?",
        answer: 2,
        options: [
          "Eating a delicious snack",
          "Viewing things",
          "State management",
        ],
        selected: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is Vue Router?",
        answer: 1,
        options: [
          "An ice cream maker",
          "A routing library for Vue",
          "Burger sauce",
        ],
        selected: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is a Prop",
        answer: 2,
        options: [
          "A prop is a function that is reusable",
          "A prop is a hook that is called by a parent?",
          "Data is passed from the parent component to the child component using Component Prop.",
        ],
        selected: null,
      },
      {
        question: "what is reactivity",
        answer: 2,
        options: [
          "When you change the data value, the page is updated to reflect the changes.",
          "React to given elements",
          "Better way to place things together and After",
        ],
        selected: null,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    quiz: [
      {
        question: "What is reactJs?",
        answer: 0,
        options: ["A framework", "A library", "A type of hat"],
        selected: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is Redux?",
        answer: 2,
        options: [
          "Eating a delicious snack",
          "Viewing things",
          "State management",
        ],
        selected: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is Material UI?",
        answer: 1,
        options: [
          "An ice cream maker",
          "A routing library for Vue",
          "Burger sauce",
        ],
        selected: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is a Prop",
        answer: 2,
        options: [
          "A prop is a function that is reusable",
          "A prop is a hook that is called by a parent?",
          "Data is passed from the parent component to the child component using Component Prop.",
        ],
        selected: null,
      },
      {
        question: "what are Hooks",
        answer: 2,
        options: [
          "When you change the data value, the page is updated to reflect the changes.",
          "React to given elements",
          "Better way to place things together and After",
        ],
        selected: null,
      },
    ],
  },
];
